<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amy&#39;s website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amy&#39;s website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Amy, and I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student at Colorado State University. I&amp;rsquo;m currently testing the efficacy of different tuberculosis vaccines in mice, and I&amp;rsquo;m working on developing an R-based data analysis pipeline for flow cytometry data. When I&amp;rsquo;m not working in the lab, I like to travel and experience new food and cultures.
LinkedIn Profile
Email: amyfox@colostate.edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outreach</title>
      <link>/outreach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/outreach/</guid>
      <description>Graduate Women in Science Outreach Committee Currently, I serve as the Graduate Women in Science Outreach Committee Co-Chair at Colorado State University. The outreach committee started in 2017 with the goal to engage community members to teach them about STEM-related topics.
I helped facilitate a Crime Scene Activity with Brownies where we
 Discussed how microbes can be used to determine the time of death of a body Participated in a microbial clock activity to determine time of death based on different microbes (candy) present  I helped Junior receive their Animal Habitats Badge when we</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Lace Tension-Controlled Compression Sock  At Rice University, my senior design team developed an adjustable compression sock that is easier to don and doff. Chronic venous disorders (CVDs) affect 40% of the U.S. population, or 128 million people, in the United States alone. Out of the patients who are prescribed medical-grade compression socks, 63% do not wear them daily, because they are difficult to put on and uncomfortable to wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>/1/01/01/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1/01/01/test/</guid>
      <description>+++ date = “2016-05-05T21:49:57-07:00” title = “Hello”
+++
Hello World!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>